Hi, Michelle.
Hello, Harry.
It's nice to see you again.
Hello.
Hi, Susan.
We have both been excited about seeing you
and having lunch with you today.
Michelle picked these flowers out for you.
Daddy, can we go soon?
We're going to go to lunch in a few minutes, honey.
But I'm thirsty.
OK. You go out and get a drink of water at the fountain.
The fountain is over there, Michelle.
Near the Exit sign.
Thank you.
Michelle is a little shy.
I used to be that way when I was her age.
Harry, if Michelle doesn't want to go,
we don't have to.
She'll be fine.
Remember,
I haven't dated any one else since her mother died.
This is a little difficult for her.
Are you ready to go?
Yes. But could you wait one minute?
I have a call to make.
Would you excuse me?
Sam, get Mr. Levine at Toytown Stores
on the telephone for me, please.
Right.
Hello. Susan Stewart calling Mr. Levine, please.
He's on the phone.
Mr. Levine, Susan Stewart.
I find myself in an embarrassing situation.
I made another lunch date for today
and forgot to enter it in my appointment book.
Can you and I meet for drinks tomorrow?
I'd really appreciate it.... Yes.... Thank you....
Tomorrow at five o'clock at the Biltmore.
I'll see you then.
Thank you, Mr. Levine.
Welcome to the South Street restaurant, folks.
What'll it be?
What do you recommend?
Well, the crab salad's always a big hit.
Susan, would you like the crab salad?
I'd love the crab salad.
Michelle, would you like to try the crab salad, too?
OK, Daddy.
We'll have three crab salads
and a pitcher of lemonade.
Help yourself to celery and carrots and other vegetables.
We used to catch crabs.
Where was that?
We had a summer house on Fire Island.
Do you remember, Michelle?
Sure.
You and Mommy used to take me on the ferryboat.
Sometimes, at night,
we would go down to the beach and catch crabs,
remember?
With a piece of meat on a string!
Right.
Well, I think I'm going to go get us all some vegetables.
There you go.
Thank you.
And some ice-cold lemonade.
Enjoy it.
Michelle, can I help you with the lemonade?
No, thank you.
I'll wait for my father.
Michelle, can we have a talk?
Sure.
I know you miss your mother.
You do?
Yes. And I'm not trying to take her place.
Then why are you and Daddy
spending so much time together?
Because we like each other.
And right now, he needs a friend.
I'm his friend.
I know you are.
Sometimes he's very sad.
And so are you, I think.
Sometimes.
I'd like to be your friend, too.
Will you let me be your friend, Michelle?
So, what were you two talking about?
Just girl talk, Daddy.
It's too hard to explain.
You're probably right.
Well, let's get started.